weightlossmother.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Natural Weight Loss | Easy Weight Loss Tips | Positive Thoughts | Emotional Eating | Healthy Food Recipes | Simple Weight Loss | Healthy Lifestyle | Self Esteem Confidence | Spiritual Weight Loss | Law of Attraction Weight Loss | Weight Loss Mother | Annette Jones |

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_pin_it_button_layout' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **186**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_pin_it_button_single_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **187**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_pin_it_button_page_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **188**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_pin_it_button_excerpt_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **189**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_username' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **206**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_follow_button_layout' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **207**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_follow_button_single_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **208**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_follow_button_page_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **209**

**Warning** : Illegal string offset 'wp_pinterest_follow_button_excerpt_display' in **/home4/iaaswie/public_html/weightlossmother.com/wp-content/plugins/wp-pinterest/includes/functions.php** on line **210**  

> Privacy Policy for Weightlossmother.com  
>  The privacy of our visitors to Weightlossmother.com is important to us.  
>  At Weightlossmother.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Weightlossmother.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.  
>  Log Files  
>  As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
>  Cookies and Web Beacons  
>  We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.  
>  We also use third party advertisements on Weightlossmother.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  
>  You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
